Guide to the Mediterranean Pilgrimage Association photograph album from the Hisham Khatib Collection AD.MC.030_ref150
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Mediterranean Pilgrimage Association
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000056; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000056e; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000056f; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Palestine; Jerusalem; Architecture; Photographic Prints
    - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000056g; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Architecture; Photographic Prints
    - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000056h; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints
    - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000056i; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Religious Sites
    - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000056j; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Maps; Jerusalem; Palestine; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000056k; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000056l; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057a; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Religious Sites; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057b; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057c; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057d; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Jerusalem; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Monuments/Memorials; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057e; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057f; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Palestine; Jerusalem; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057g; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Fountains; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites; Buildings; Palestine; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057h; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Palestine; Jerusalem; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057i; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Architecture; Buildings; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057j; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057k; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Palestine; Jerusalem; English Writing; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Photographic Prints; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057l; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057m; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Palestine; Jerusalem; Religious Sites; Architecture; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057n; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Palestine; Jerusalem; English Writing; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057o; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Mosques; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; Palestine; Jerusalem; Photographic Prints
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057p; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Palestine; Jerusalem; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057q; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Mosques; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Photographic Prints
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057r; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Palestine; Jerusalem; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Fountains; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Printed Materials
    - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem", 1927; ref150_000057s; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - Postcards of Bethany, Jericho and the Tomb of Lazarus., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000058; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Albumen Prints; Jericho; Al-Eizariya/Bethany; Buildings; Streets/Roads; English Writing; French Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Women; Children; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Sites; Palestine; West Bank; Landscapes
  - Postcards of Rachel's Tomb and Solomon's Pools., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000059; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Bethlehem; Tombs/Mausoleums; Solomon's Pools/El-Burak; Religious Sites; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; West Bank; Bilal bin Rabah Mosque/Rachel's Tomb; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Mountains/Hills
  - Three postcards of the Church of the Nativity., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000060; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Churches; Church of the Nativity; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Religious Imagery; Bethlehem; West Bank; Palestine
  - Two postcards of Bethlehem., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000061; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Bethlehem; Palestine; West Bank; Christmas; Crowds; Parades/Processions; Buildings; Agriculture/Farms; Religious Holiday; Religious Ceremony
  - Postcards of Bethlehem and the Dead Sea., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000062; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Bethlehem; West Bank; Palestine; Buildings; Men; Weapons; Guns; Animals; Lakes; Dead Sea; English Writing; French Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; Regional/National Dress; Architecture
  - Two postcards of Nazareth., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000063; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Nazareth; Palestine; Buildings; Religious Sites; Synagogues; Architecture; English Writing; Churches; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills
  - Two postcards of Nazareth., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000064; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Albumen Prints; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; English Writing; Nazareth; Palestine; Religious Imagery; Group Portraits; Mountains/Hills
  - Two postcards of Mary's Well (Virgin's Fountain)., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000065; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Nazareth; Palestine; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Women; Children; Girls; Boys; Mary's Well/Ain il-Adhra; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Animals; Camels; Regional/National Dress; French Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; Water
  - Two postcards of Nazareth., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000066; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Nazareth; Palestine; English Writing; French Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; Buildings; Mount Tabor/Jabal at-Tur; Landscapes
  - Two postcards of Nazareth., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000067; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Nazareth; Palestine; Hotels; English Writing; Landscapes
  - Postcards of Tiberias and Hebron., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000068; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Sea of Galilee/Lake Tiberias; Lakes; Buildings; Tiberias/Tabariyyah; Palestine; Hebron/Al-Khalil; West Bank; Men; Animals; Mountains/Hills
  - Postcards of Haifa and Tiberias., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000069; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; English Writing; French Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Sea of Galilee/Lake Tiberias; Lakes; Tiberias/Tabariyyah; Palestine; Haifa; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Buildings; Mount Carmel /Al-Karmil; Mountains/Hills
  - Postcards of Mount Tabor and Jaffa., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000070; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Mount Tabor/Jabal at-Tur; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Palestine; Jaffa; French Writing; English Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; Mediterranean Sea; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; Samaria/as-Sāmirah
  - Two postcards of Haifa and Mt. Carmel., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000071; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Palm Trees; Mount Carmel /Al-Karmil; Haifa; Palestine; Landscapes; Men; Hats; Buildings; Mountains/Hills; Religious Sites; French Writing; English Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing
  - A postcard titled "Flowers from the Holy Land"., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000072; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; English Writing; Palestine
  - Postcards of Cana of Galilee and Jacob's Well., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000073; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; English Writing; Individual Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Outdoors; Buildings; Galilee; Palestine; Greek Writing; French Writing; Chandeliers; Religious Imagery; West Bank; Nablus; Religious Sites; Albumen Prints; Jacob's Well/Bir Ya'qub; Priests/Clergymen
  - (Blank page), Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000074; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000075; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - An advertisement for Antonaides Brothers travel agency in Larnaca, Cyprus, and a ticket for a shore excursion from the Mantovani Tourist Agency., 11 May 1928; ref150_000076; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    English Writing; Larnaca, Cyprus; Advertisements; Printed Materials
  - Map of Sea of Galilee and the Dead Sea from Thomas Cook & Son., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000077; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Maps; English Writing; Galilee; Palestine; Dead Sea; Beirut, Lebanon; Damascus, Syria; Petra, Jordan; Printed Materials
  - Reuters news bulletin to Cyprus., 8 May 1928; ref150_000078; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    English Writing; Newspaper Clippings; Cyprus
  - Reuters news bulletin to Cyprus., 10 May 1928; ref150_000079; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - Three postcards of Smyrne (Izmir)., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000080; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Izmir, Turkey; Smyrna; Religious Sites; Mosques; Buildings; Architecture; Aegean Sea; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Carriages/Coaches; Men; Streets/Roads; French Writing
  - Two postcards of Smyrne (Izmir) Port., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000081; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; French Writing; Izmir, Turkey; Ports; Smyrna; Aegean Sea; Seas; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Carriages/Coaches
  - Two postcards of Smyrne (Izmir)., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000082; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Smyrna; Izmir, Turkey; Aegean Sea; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; French Writing
  - (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000083; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000084; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000085; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), produced by the National Turkish Tourist Agency, 1928; ref150_000086a; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Arabic Calligraphy; Books; Hotels; Printed Materials
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086b; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Printed Materials
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086c; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Bosphorus; Seas; Boats/Ships; Buildings
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086d; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Bosphorus; Men; Buildings; Forts/Castles; Roumeli Hissar Castle; Printed Materials
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086e; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Hippodrome of Constantinople; Hagia Sophia; Religious Sites; Architecture; Arabic Calligraphy; Buildings; Monuments/Memorials; Printed Materials
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086f; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Istanbul, Turkey; Constantinople; English Writing; Blue Mosque/Sultan Ahmed Mosque; Architecture; Religious Sites; Mosques; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Reservoirs; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Printed Materials
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086g; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Religious Sites; Mosques; Suleymaniye Mosque; Arabic Calligraphy; Tombs/Mausoleums; Coffins/Caskets; Statues/Sculptures; Museums; Printed Materials
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086h; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Constantinople; Photographic Prints; Prinkipo/Büyükada (Turkey); Landscapes; Prince Islands, Istanbul, Turkey; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Bosphorus; Suleymaniye Mosque; Mosques; Religious Sites; English Writing; Buildings; Architecture; The Golden Horn/Haliç
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086i; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; Constantinople; The Golden Horn/Haliç; Boats/Ships; Flags; Transportation; Bosphorus; Mountains/Hills; Printed Materials
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086j; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; Istanbul, Turkey; Constantinople; English Writing; Group Portraits; Turbans; Men; Outdoors; Regional/National Dress; Buildings; Architecture; Printed Materials
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086k; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; Constantinople; Photographic Prints; Seas; Buildings; Dolmabahce Palace; Architecture; Palaces; Bosphorus
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086l; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Bridges; Galata, Istanbul, Turkey; New Mosque / Yeni Cami; Mosques; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Crowds; Street Lamps; Beyazit Square, Istanbul, Turkey; Beyazit Tower; Photographic Prints; Transportation; Trams
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086m; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books; English Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; Constantinople; Grand Bazaar; Shops; Men; Photographic Prints; Markets
    - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul), 1928; ref150_000086n; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
      Books
  - A postcard of Brasserie Universelle Restaurant, Paris., Circa 1928; ref150_000087; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Postcards; Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Paris, France; French Writing; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Men; Women; Hats; Restaurants/bars; Buildings; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps
  - (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000088; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000089; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
  - Newspaper clipping with an image of an entrance to the Shwedagon Pagoda., Circa 1928; ref150_000090; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Newspaper Clippings; Architecture; Buildings; English Writing; Religious Sites; Temples; Men; Regional/National Dress; Statues/Sculptures; Shwedagon Pagoda; Yangon, Myanmar
  - Inside Back Cover- Newspaper clipping about the Shwedagon Pagoda "Prayers at Buddhist Shrine by Robert Esmond."., Circa 1928; ref150_000091; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)
    Newspaper Clippings; Newspapers/Magazines; English Writing; Shwedagon Pagoda; Yangon, Myanmar; Temples; Religious Sites
  - Back Cover., Circa 1900-1928; ref150_000092; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: ad_mc_030_ref150)